<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ZipRyde</string>
    <string name="signup">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="loginup">Login</string>


    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="place_details">&lt;b&gt;%1$s&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;Place Id: %2$s&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Address: %3$s&lt;br/&gt;Phone: %4$s&lt;br/&gt;Website: %5$s</string>

    <string name="google_maps_key" templateMergeStrategy="preserve" translatable="false">
        AIzaSyA-vFXMTW1Hrtk0Nl_xkwbwqnTl6LFYmyk
    </string>

    <string name="google_maps_key_trivecta" templateMergeStrategy="preserve" translatable="false">
        AIzaSyBqwOXCatvgb_ZaA77-A3pmgj3Klid5Y7Q
    </string>

    <string name="google_maps_key_zipryde" templateMergeStrategy="preserve" translatable="false">
        AIzaSyBziXe7fpyyLNcv5i_TMvBEJCF54SekdBw
    </string>


    <!-- General strings-->
    <string name="firstname">First Name</string>
    <string name="lastname">Last Name</string>
    <string name="email">E-Mail</string>
    <string name="mobileno">Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="enterotp">Enter OTP</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="newpassword">New Password</string>
    <string name="confirmpassword">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="change">CHANGE</string>
    <string name="offer">Offer</string>
    <string name="currencysymbol">$</string>
    <string name="gps_start">Starts Here</string>
    <string name="gps_end">Ends Here</string>
    <string name="distanceunit">mi</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>


    <!-- Button name -->
    <string name="btn_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="btn_resend">Resend</string>
    <string name="btn_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="btn_close">Close</string>
    <string name="btn_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="btn_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="btn_no">No</string>
    <string name="btn_open">Open</string>
    <string name="btn_done">DONE</string>
    <string name="btn_accept">Accept</string>


    <!-- Login screen -->
    <string name="signin">Sign In</string>
    <string name="forgetpwd">Forget Password?</string>
    <string name="registerasnew">Register As New</string>

    <!-- Signup screen -->
    <string name="alreadyhaveaccount">Already have an Account?</string>
    <string name="signup_validmobileno">Please enter valid Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="signup_fname">Please enter the First Name</string>
    <string name="signup_lname">Please enter the Last Name</string>
    <string name="signup_emailid">Please enter the Email Id</string>
    <string name="signup_validemailid">Please enter the Email Id in a valid format</string>
    <string name="signup_pwd">Please enter the Password</string>
    <string name="signup_confimrpwd">Please enter the Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="signup_pwdnotmatch">Password and Confirm Password are not matching</string>


    <!-- Verify Pin Screen-->
    <string name="verifypin_pleaseentercode">Please enter code sent to</string>
    <string name="verifypin_yourmobileno">your Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="btn_resendcode">Resend Code</string>
    <string name="btn_changeno">Change Number</string>

    <!-- Forgot password screen-->
    <string name="forgotpassword_entercode">Please enter code</string>
    <string name="forgotpassword_code">CODE</string>
    <string name="forgotpassword_verify">VERIFY</string>
    <string name="forgotpassword_generateotp">Generate OTP</string>
    <string name="forgotpassword_entermobileno">Please enter Mobile number</string>
    <string name="forgotpassword_generate">GENERATE</string>


    <!-- Home Map Screen -->

    <string name="homemap_whereto">Where to?</string>
    <string name="homemap_selectpickup">Select Pickup Location</string>

    <!-- Navigation Menu -->
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_menu">ZIPRYDE</string>
    <string name="navimenu_bookride">Book ZipRyde</string>
    <string name="navimenu_yourride">Your ZipRydes</string>
    <string name="navimenu_help">Help</string>
    <string name="navimenu_payemntsetup">Payment Setup</string>
    <string name="navimenu_paypal">Paypal</string>
    <string name="navimenu_cashapp">Cash App</string>
    <string name="navimenu_logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="navimenu_airlinevoucher">Airline Voucher</string>
    <string name="navimenu_airlinevouchermsg">We will take vouchers from any airline to provide transportation for passengers.Upon entering the ZipRyde customer will hand it over to the driver. \n ZipTips are appreciated.</string>


    <!-- From-To selection screen-->
    <string name="fromto_fromlocation">Enter place to search</string>
    <string name="fromto_droplocaiton">Enter the drop location</string>


    <!-- Cash Display  screen -->

    <string name="cashdisplay_totalfair">Total Fare</string>
    <string name="cashdisplay_totaldist">Total Distance</string>
    <string name="cashdisplay_total">Total</string>
    <string name="cashdisplay_paybyusing">Pay by using</string>
    <string name="cashdisplay_cash">Cash</string>
    <string name="cashdisplay_cc">Credit Card</string>
    <string name="cashdisplay_dc">Debit Card</string>
    <string name="cashdisplay_nb">Netbanking</string>


    <!-- Direction Confirmation Screen -->
    <string name="directionconf_notavailable">Not Available</string>
    <string name="directionconf_defaultseats">Seats 1\-4</string>
    <string name="directionconf_defaultseats2">Seats 1\-7</string>

    <string name="directionconf_noservice">The service is not available for the selected route</string>

    <string name="directionconf_getzipfare">GET ZIP FARE</string>
    <string name="directionconf_cabtype1">Micro</string>
    <string name="directionconf_cabtype2">Sedan</string>
    <string name="directionconf_cabtype3">SUV</string>
    <string name="directionconf_selectvehicle">Select vehicle type</string>
    <string name="directionconf_zipmenow">ZIP ME NOW</string>
    <string name="directionconf_selectseats">Select Your Seats</string>
    <string name="directionconf_nameyourprice">Name your own price</string>
    <string name="directionconf_suggprice">Suggested price</string>
    <string name="directionconf_fareprice">Fare Price</string>
    <string name="directionconf_zipnotavailable">ZipRyde is currently unavailable in the vicinity of the pickup location.</string>
    <string name="directionconf_zipextrachargesmsg">Not including waiting time, tolls and surcharge</string>

    <!-- Driver Tracking Page-->
    <string name="driverinfo_call">Call</string>
    <string name="driverinfo_zipstatus">ZipRyde Status</string>


    <!-- User dialog Messages titles -->
    <string name="warning">Warning</string>
    <string name="success">Success</string>
    <string name="failure">Failure</string>
    <string name="information">Information</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="bookingsuccess">Booking Successful</string>


    <!-- User Information-->

    <string name="usermsg_locationturnon">Please turn ON location services in your device.</string>
    <string name="usermsg_successfullogin">Successfully logged in</string>
    <string name="usermsg_wanttologout">Are you sure you want to Log Out?</string>
    <string name="usermsg_successfullyregistered"> Successfully Registered</string>
    <string name="usermsg_bookingcancelled">Sorry, Unable to grab the request. Hint: Try with a higher fare</string>
    <string name="usermsg_waitdriveraccept">Please wait till the driver accepts your request</string>
    <string name="usermsg_ziprydecancelled">Your ZipRyde has been cancelled.</string>
    <string name="usermsg_querysubmit">Your query has been successfully submitted</string>
    <string name="usermsg_permissiondenied">Permission denied</string>
    <string name="usermsg_bookingsuccessfull_waitdriver">Your Booking request has been submitted successfully. Please wait till driver accepts.</string>
    <string name="usermsg_driveraccepted">Get Ready! Driver is on the Way.</string>
    <string name="usermsg_driverscheduleaccepted">Your trip has been scheduled Successfully.</string>
    <string name="usermsg_nodriveravailable">available \/ Driver Not accepted the request. Try after sometime</string>
    <string name="usermsg_cashmsg">Thank you for choosing ZipRyde.\nWe hope you will ride with us in the future!\nWe would appreciate referrals to all of your friends, family and associates.</string>
    <string name="usermsg_ccmsg">Thank you for choosing ZipRyde.We hope you will ride with us in the future!\nFor credit card payment, your driver will be able to process your card in a Zip!\n!Zip Tips are greatly appreciated!</string>
    <string name="usermsg_tripcompletedreminder">Reminder! Check your belongings before exiting  the vehicle</string>

    <!-- Error Messages -->

    <string name="errmsg_network_noconnection">Either there is no network connectivity or server is not available. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="errmsg_nolocationfound">Couldn\'t get the current location. Please wait.</string>
    <string name="errmsg_googleapi">Could not connect to Google API Client</string>
    <string name="errmsg_sessionexpired">Your session has expired. Please re-login!</string>


    <string-array name="sedan_micro_array">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="suv_array">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="disclaimer_text">Please read the terms of this disclaimer carefully – it contains important information about the transportation services we provide, your rights and limits, and our obligations to you.
        \n &#8226;  THE ZIPRYDE Drivers AND ZipRyde Vehicles ARE PROVIDED by the ZipRyde platform to facilitate the ride. ZipRyde is a service provider connecting Taxicab and Limo Drivers to users through our software platform.
        \n &#8226;  All of our drivers including taxi and limo go through a rigorous permitting process which includes
Criminal background checks and their vehicles must meet all the requirements of the licensing agencies.
        \n &#8226;  When you book with us you will specify a pick-up time.  We will do what we can to arrive at the agreed time, but the unknowns and unforeseen events associated with road transport means we cannot guarantee that will happen.
        \n &#8226;	This Agreement governs your use of the ZipRyde application, our website, the Support hotline and technology platform (collectively, the “ZipRyde Platform”).  In many jurisdictions, the right to operate the ZipRyde Platform is licensed by ZipRyde Inc. to its relevant Affiliates, and the relevant Affiliate in your jurisdiction provides you the right to access and use the ZipRyde Platform in your jurisdiction.  Where no Affiliate exists in your jurisdiction but use of the ZipRyde Platform is available to you, the right to access and use the ZipRyde Platform will be provided to you by ZipRyde, Inc.
        \n &#8226;	ZipRyde is not a transportation provider.  ZipRyde provides a software application, the ZipRyde Platform, and support for the transportation services.  You may utilize the ZipRyde Platform to obtain and/or provide taxi, limo, or other licensed transportation services.  In case of an accident or other incident, all claims should be handled through the relevant policies which you establish for your firm and any and all subcontractors working for you.
        \n &#8226;	ZipRyde is a service provider connecting Taxicab and Limo Drivers to users through our software platform. Taxi and Limousine vehicles are registered, insured, and permitted by the city and airport authority in their area. Our Company ( ZipRyde)  will keep a copy of the insurance on  all vehicles  which will be provided upon request, This is a requirement of the licensing agencies.
        \n &#8226;	All complaints need to be first directed to the licensing agencies.
        \n &#8226;	You are responsible for ensuring that the pick-up time you have requested allows you sufficient time to reach your destination, taking into account unexpected events.
        \n &#8226;	Please be aware that there are numerous factors that we cannot prevent against and which may impact or delay your journey with us.  For these reasons our service is provided on the basis that we are not responsible for any inconveniences, losses you suffer, costs you incur or other consequences arising from our failure to provide, or delays in providing, our agreed services because of factors which could be considered to be outside our reasonable control.  Factors outside of our reasonable control include (but are not limited to) adverse weather conditions; accidents involving our vehicles; delays caused by traffic congestion, road work, road closures, accidents or diversions; or mechanical breakdowns.
        \n&#8226;	You understand that being a passenger in this vehicle has risks and hazards.  You have requested on your own to be a passenger and to hire this vehicle for transportation.  You hereby hold the ZipRyde harmless from any loss, liability, damage or costs.  You agree to release, waive, and discharge the ZipRyde of this vehicle of any responsibility for loss, or personal injury or death that may be sustained by you, or any loss to personal property owned by you, as a result of being a passenger in this vehicle.
        \n&#8226;	ZipRyde does provide a lost and found service to all passengers by submitting a request for the missing items through the ZipRyde App.
        \n&#8226;	User agree to pay the ZipRyde amount directly to the drivers at the end of the trip with an acceptable form of payments which are cash, credit cards, PayPal. Airlines vouchers or through cash app application.
    </string>

    <string name="help_text">\t There is no need for you to go outside and submit yourself to the hot,rain or cold.With only your smart phone you can choose your pickup location with one tap or just enter your address manually.
        \n\t With one more tap your ZipRyde car is locked from their pickup location. Then by setting a drop-off point, you get a quote for the journey based on your pricing tariff to avid price haggling and you can also track the driver\'s estimate time of arrival.
        \n\n website: www.zipryde.com
\n Email: help@zipryde.com
\n Tel: 1-800-609-9070\t press 3 for help</string>

    <string name="warrantydisclamier_text">\tWarranty and disclaimer

\n\nWE ENDEAVOUR TO PROVIDE THE BEST SERVICE WE CAN, BUT YOU UNDERSTAND AND
AGREE THAT THE ZIPRYDE SERVICE IS PROVIDED “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE”,
WITHOUT EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OR CONDITION OF ANY KIND. YOU USE THE
ZIPRYDE SERVICE AT YOUR OWN RISK. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY
APPLICABLE LAW, ZIPRYDE AND ALL OWNERS OF THE CONTENT MAKE NO
REPRESENTATIONS AND DISCLAIM ANY WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF
SATISFACTORY QUALITY, SERVICES BY OUR INDEPENDENT CONTRACTORS FOR A
PARTICULAR PURPOSE. NEITHER ZIPRYDE OR ANY OWNERS OF CONTENT WARRANTS
THAT THE ZIPRYDE SERVICE IS FREE OF MALWARE OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.
IN ADDITION, ZIPRYDE MAKES NO REPRESENTATION NOR DOES IT WARRANT, ENDORSE,
GUARANTEE, OR ASSUME RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY THIRD PARTY CONTRACTED WITH
(OR THE THEREOF), USER CONTENT, OR ANY OTHER PRODUCT OR SERVICE ADVERTISED
OR OFFERED BY A THIRD PARTY ON OR THROUGH THE ZIPRYDE SERVICE OR ANY
HYPERLINKED WEBSITE OF ITS CONTRACTORS, OR FEATURED IN ANY BANNER OR
OTHER ADVERTISING. YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ZIPRYDE IS NOT
RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR ANY TRANSACTION, SERVICE PROVIDED BETWEEN YOU
AND THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS OF THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS OR PRODUCT AND
OR SERVICE PROVIDED BY THIRD PARTY OR OUR INDEPENDENT CONTRACTORS OR
SERVICE ADVERTISED ON OUR THROUGH THE ZIPRYDE SERVICE. AS WITH ANY
PURCHASE OF PRODUCT OR SERVICE THROUGH ANY MEDIUM OR IN ANY
ENVIRONMENT,YOU SHOULD USE YOUR JUDGMENT AND EXERCISE CAUTION WHERE
APPROPRIATE. NO ADVISE OR INFORMATION WHETHER ORAL OR IN WRITING OBTAINED
BY YOU FROM ZIPRYDE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY ON BEHALF OF ZIPRYDE IN
THIS REGARD. SOME ASPECTS OF THIS SECTION MAY NOT APPLY IN SOME
JURISDICTIONS IF PROHIBITED BY APPLICABLE LAW.
ALL COMPLAINTS NEED TO BE DIRECTED TO CITIES AND REGULATED AGENCIES WHERE
CONTRACTOR HAS A LICENSE THAT IS DISPLAYED INSIDE THE VEHICLE,
CONSUMER MUST VERIFY THE VEHICLE AND INFORMATION GIVEN TO BY ZIPRYDE
WHEN THE BOOKING COMPLETED.
ZIPRYDE CANNOT GUARANTEE ANY ACTIONS CAUSED BY THE INDEPENDENT
CONTRACTOR AFTER THE BOOKING IS COMPLETE.
ZIPRYDE SHALL NOT ACCEPT ANY PAYMENTS FROM THE CONSUMERS. ALL THE
PAYMENT SHALL BE PAID TO THE SERVICE PROVIDER. CONSUMER AGREES TO
INDEMNIFY ZIPRYDE AFTER THE BOOKING IS COMPLETE AND ASSUMES THEIR OWN
RISK THEREAFTER.

ZIPRYDE HAS NOT PROMISE TO YOU EXCEPT TO FIND YOU AN INDEPENDENT
CONTRACTOR DRIVER AND ALL LIABILITIES THEREAFTER RESTS WITH THE SAID
CONTRACTOR.
THIS DOES NOT AFFECT YOUR STATUTORY RIGHTS AS A CONSUMER.</string>


</resources>
